Anggriawan Rayzadmiko

Bogor Regency, West Java | +6281310008091 | anggriawan.net@gmail.com | https://linkedin.com/in/anggriawanr | https://razd-net.vercel.app

Summary

A fresh graduate in System and Instrumentation Physics, who has great interest in Web Development and UI/UX. Also known as hard-working college student which loves to solving problem, troubleshooting, and have great attention of detail. Have 1 year experience designing UI and social media in Exedu Start-up Project, create awesome and up-to-date UI design to web with Figma.

Experience

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 **BRIN**

Research Assistant

Modeled and developed a PID controller using Raspberry Pi programmed with Python and tuning it, achieve a very stable response on rocket flight

Exedu Start-Up Project

Jul 2021 - Jul 2022

Graphics Design

- Designed a website and create the prototype with figma
- Designed a google based website (Google Sites) that have more than 1500 users
- Created a website prototype in Figma and collaborated with Product Manager Designed attractive content design to reach the public in instagram

Universitas Indonesia

Feb - Jul 2022

Control System Laboratory Assistant

Evaluated practitioner's competence in the form of a presentation Trained practitioners about control theory in practice with microcontroller and data acquisition software

Education

Universitas Indonesia

Graduated: Jul 2022

Bachelor of Science - Physics

GPA 3.51

Thesis Research: Design of Cold Probe Temperature Controller on Thermoelectric Material Characterization System using Microcontroller

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- ReactJS
- Python

- Git
- **NextJS**
- UI/UX
- MongoDB
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Figma
- Prisma ORM

Organization and Volunteer

Physics Department Student Association

Feb 2020 - Feb 2021

Staff

Designed attractive content to reach the public in instagram and students

Pesta Rakyat Fisika (PRF)

Jan - Februari 2020

Staff of Quiz Competition at Elementary School Level Designed attractive and interactive question with PowerPoint

Certificate

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript Dicoding, 2023

- Belajar Membuat Front-End Web untuk Pemula Dicoding, 2023
- **Python Essentials 1** Cisco, 2022
- **Python Essentials 2** Cisco, 2022